dialindia.com 2016-03-05

# Privacy Policy - Dialindia.com

**Introduction**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
We are firmly committed to safeguarding your privacy in conjunction with your use of the dialindia.com website. This Privacy Policy addresses the privacy of visitors to the Dialindia.com website and identifies the type of data and information we collects from visitors, how we use and disclose it, and the steps we take to secure your privacy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal or organization's information will be treated as you use our service. This policy may change from time to time as we update current services or add new services, so please check back.

 **Information Collection**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
The dialindia.com website collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site. Some personal and business information is gathered when you voluntarily register your business or entity. During registration, we ask for contact names, titles, addresses, email addresses, industry classification and details on your company products and services. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better service we can provide. Once you register you are no longer anonymous us - you are given a User ID and you are able to take full advantage of Dialindia.com member offerings. You can also edit or update your Dialindia.com Account Information at any time.

We may also collect non-personal information about your visit, such as the domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered our site, how much time you spend on each page, and the IP address associated with your computer.

(a) Internet Cookies and Related Technologies  
We may use cookies to improve the content delivered to you while you are on our website. Cookies do not contain or capture any personal information but it may capture computer identification information. Your decision to refuse cookies from dialindia.com will not prevent you from using our site, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of our advanced features.

(b) Third Party Advertisers and External Links  
The dialindia.com website contains advertisements from third-party advertisers or provides links to external websites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Our partners or advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit our site. Any third party cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the website/company placing them.

**Use of   Information**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
dialindia.com uses the information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, complete your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and / or provide statistical reporting for internal and external customers.

dialindia.com may use aggregated information about how visitors use our web site and disclose this information with our partners and related third parties in order to improve our website and attract advertisers and listings. For example, we may share how many individuals visit the website and on average how long they stay on each page. Such use and sharing of aggregated information does not disclose any of your personal information to third parties.

dialindia.com does not rent, sell, disclose or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products, services, or information you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

dialindia.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view an ad.

**Security Measures**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
dialindia.com takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your information. We use commercially reasonable computer security safeguards to protect its databases and servers against risks of loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, or inadvertent or improper disclosure of data. We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Services. No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any firewalls or secure server software we may deploy. dialindia.com continues to evaluate and implement enhancements in security technology and practices; however we can only take steps to help reduce the risks of unauthorized access.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as technical support services. To perform those functions, it may be necessary for them to obtain access to our databases and servers, which may contain personally identifying information about users. We will not provide your account information to any third party except as described in this Privacy Policy or with your consent. These parties are obliged to use the information according to our instructions and they are bound to this Privacy Policy and must apply appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

By using this website or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

**Privacy and Security Policy Updates**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
This Privacy and Security Policy supersedes and replaces all previously posted Privacy and Security Policies. dialindia.com reserves the right to update this Privacy and Security Policy to reflect any changes at any time.

If you have any questions about the privacy of your personal information please **[ contact us](http://www.dialindia.com/about/contact.html "contact us").**
